This is Yuu Yamazaki from BEYONDZ Rain Forest, Kawakami, Japan.
I'm Yuu Yamazaki from Kawakami.
As of this year's spring tour
I will be graduating from BEYONDZ and Hello Project.
In the course of our activities as BEYONDZ
I have been inspired by all the members around me
I want to learn more about the songs I love to sing
I decided to study in a different environment
I decided to graduate from BEYONDZ to study in a different environment.
I will continue to do my best so that I can give a performance that will make people think that BEYONDZ is the best from today to tomorrow, and from tomorrow to the day after that.
Please continue to support Yuhane Yamazaki and the Beyons!
Hello! This time I'll be performing with Risa Irie of Juice Chus and
and Yumi Kasai from Tsubaki Factory!
This time, we'll be talking about the two of them, so please bear with us until the end.
Please bear with us until the end.
Okay, so we're the same age as you.
Yes, we are.
Recently, we tend to work alone or in groups.
We don't get to be together very often.
Yes, but...
But...
Yes.
At the winter concert, we sometimes see each other in the hallway and say good morning.
We're good friends, and I really miss our auditions.
I talked with Risa Irie a lot during the auditions, so we did.
Even though we're in different groups, we're still in the same group as Juice=Juice.
We were both doing our best in different groups.
I hope we can be good rivals and have friendly competition with each other.
Our spring tour will start soon!
Juice=Juice will start on April 20.
and Tsubaki Factory will start on May 3.
On this tour, we will be joined by the leader of each group.
Juice=Juice will be led by Akari Uemura
and Makisora Niino of Tsubaki Factory will be graduating.
How do you feel about that?
Yes, I think so.
I don't know about this tour.
I know the set list.
I know the setlist, but for those who have been supporting Juice=Juice since the days of Ms. Uemura and the original members
I think the setlist has a lot of exciting moments for those who have been supporting Juice=Juice since the days of Ms. Uemura and the original members.
Mr. Uemura's amazing costumes, etc.
It seems that Mr. Uemura thought about the setlist together with the staff.
I'm sure you will receive a lot of love from Mr. Uemura.
All in all
10 people
We will be performing 22 shows in 11 locations.
The 23rd concert will be Uemura-san's graduation concert.
I'd like to introduce you to Uemura-san's favorite 23.
And the title of the concert...
It's called "One Line".
It also means that we should all stand together as one line
It also means that we should all work together as one line and do our best in FY11.
With this kind of enthusiasm, I would like to do my best on the spring tour.
It's wonderful!
Thank you very much.
Tsubaki Factory is
As of this moment, we haven't decided on the release of the album yet.
We haven't decided on the release yet, but the title of the tour
The title of the tour is
Come On Everybody.
The title of the tour is "Come On Everybody".
Stay
Stay Free & Stay Tuned.
Kisora Shinnuma said "Come On Everybody" at the beginning of the song.
It's also the title of the tour from the beginning.
Every moment and every Tsubaki Factory
I want to do my best to give a performance that will make people think that we are the best and the strongest in every moment.
And since Ms. Shinnuma is graduating
I hope to give such a wonderful performance that you will never forget this tour in your life.
I hope I can give you a wonderful performance that you will never forget in your life.
I will do my best!
Please take a look at this video.
Please take a look.
This is the first day of the tour. Everyone has worked a lot.
For me, I have come to the end of my first day.
I can assure you that we will be fine, so let's all do our best so that we can showcase our skills.
Yes!
Everyone is cool.
Let's do our best!
Yes!
Here we go!
RikaCon!
NES!
Guys!
Rin!
Kero!
No!
Danya!
Pei!
Yup!
Haneda!
Keep your smile!
me
me me me
Thank you for watching!
It's a tear-jerker of a movie.
I'm jealous of you, I'm jealous of you, I'm jealous of you, I'm jealous of you.
I can't say that the world is a strange place
My heart is thirsty and scared
I weep with a sense of humanity
Overlapping with heroes
Chencheng, sasso, show cue
Give me the chance of great love
Weeping of Humanity's Sense
Someone make my eyes hot
Love and sympathy
If you don't get on board, there's no loss
One life for one person
One person, one feeling
Telepathy
No one will ever know
I'm sick of my ass
A melody that's popped out
I can't get into your features
Oh yeah!
I can't do it! I can't do it!
Yes, we!
At our place.
No! No!
Since when?
Since when do we have permission?
They're interrupting.
I'm kicking their asses.
But it's not their kid.
You're so twisted.
It's my gaze... and nothing else.
Not at all. Grade 5 sensitivity.
FTD on the right
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
It's easy to be one of them when you're in on it
too kind a sympathy unbreakable scene that takes off
Complicated life, complicated emotion
Delicacy, too kind, too average.
What is it if you're out of the loop on the day you're dropped?
Complicated lives, complicated emotions.
Delicacy, too kind, too average
Oh yeah, don't cry, don't cry
Yes we yes we
Don't let go
Oh yeah, don't cry, don't cry
Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
Just make that
Kiloin over and over Big bosom temperature
Somebody make my eyes hot
I'm too cheap and it won't save me
Life was too complicated, feelings were too complicated
A mean that's too mean
I've been dropped by a tree, I've fallen back, I've stuck out.
No love, no passing, too fretful for nothing
One life, one emotion, one feeling
No one knows what to do
I can't lose my ass if I can get in a moment, it's a victory
Cry, cry, cry, cry
YES! WE! YES! WE!
Don't let me in on you guys
Oh yeah!
Cry, cry, cry, cry
YES! WE! YES! WE!
To the impact of the original
Cry, cry, cry, cry!
Cry, cry, cry, cry, cry, cry
HUH!
Cry, cry, cry, cry, cry, cry, weep, weep, weep, weep, weep, weep, weep
HUH! PE jetzt!
Cry, cry, cry, cry, cry
HUH! HUH!
luk говорят
Angulum's Spring Tour Secret Secret has started.
Thank you very much. So, this is the last tour for me,
But I don't really feel like it's the last time, so I'm doing it one more time with the same feeling,
I think it would make everyone uncomfortable, so I would like everyone to see the current Angstrom in the big lottery.
There are so many things that only the current 11 members can bring out,
And it's not just in terms of expression, there are many scenes like that during the live,
I would be happy if you could come to see us and enjoy our performances,
I would be happy if you could come and see us, and I hope that you would enjoy seeing us,
I would be happy if you could come to the show and look forward to seeing us,
I hope we can bring you happiness,
I hope we can bring you our own love, smiles, and happiness until the very end.
Let's make this a fun space together.
I'll be waiting for you. There are still many places to go,
We are still in the first day of the tour, but we are going to have a lot of fun,
If you have time, I would be very happy if you could come and visit us.
We will make you happy.
We'll be waiting for you. Bye bye.
Yay.
Risa Irie of Juice=Juice and Yumi Kasai of Tsubaki Factory present "Halo! Stay.
From here I would like to talk a little bit about each other. I will ask you some questions, so don't think too much and answer in a quick tempo.
Yumi is the new Yamanashi Ambassador. What do you recommend for Yamanashi in spring? Suko Fujimoto Resort.
She joined the shuffle unit Good Mix. What did you notice about working with different members?
Each group has its own color. What do you think has changed since the junior members joined the group?
I have tried my best to teach the younger members how to dance and sing.
What has changed since I turned 20 is that I can make some decisions on my own.
I'm trying my best to let as many people as possible know the charm of hockey.
So, you have a new junior member, and this is the first time you have a junior member as a group, but have there been any specific changes in your mindset?
I also joined the group as a general member, so I am not sure if there are any specific changes in your mindset or not.
I joined the group as an ordinary member, so all three of the new members are ordinary members, so learning to dance and sing was a struggle for me in the beginning.
So I thought I would do my best to give them advice on how they could improve their dancing and singing.
I felt like I could do my best to give advice to the new members who were participating in the dance lesson.
I was invited to a dance lesson where new members were participating.
I was invited to a dance lesson once where a new member was participating, and I was able to teach dance to someone for the first time, so it was easy for me to understand how to do it better and how to explain it better.
I thought a lot about how I could explain dance in an easy-to-understand way so that I could teach.
I want to work harder on my own performance and I think I can also grow by teaching younger students.
Fuji Motsusco Resort has a festival called Fuji Shiba Cherry Blossom Festival from April 15, and the flowers are so beautiful that I can see the flowers with Mr. Fuji.
The festival is held from April 15 to 15 in April, and the flowers are so beautiful that you can see them with Mr. Fuji.
And this Fuji Shiba Cherry Blossom Festival is only held in the spring, so please stop by when you go to Kawaguchiko.
If you go to Kawaguchiko, please stop by and ask Risa-chan a question after the vtr.
Haloste!
Getchu!
Shanwei dance, is it because of the summer?
Batcha batcha batcha batcha batcha batcha batcha batcha batcha batcha batcha batcha batcha batcha batcha
Tea no oma, first album, Channel 1, on sale now!
Kono nyona dame, kokoro no overflow nai
Tears of Heroine Get off, I declare I'm getting off Topinorei
Smylight, whatever the end point is...
Haloste
Next, I'd like to ask Risa-chan a question.
Yes, I'll do my best
Risa released her first photo book on Valentine's Day this year.
Do you have any behind-the-scenes stories?
I made myself fit for the first time and took on the challenge of removing salt from my body.
Risa loves muscle training. Are there any muscles you are interested in now?
My stomach is often visible in my costumes.
I want to work hard so that the vertical lines of my abdominal muscles look nice.
That's so cool!
What do you want to do with the juice juice in your current position?
Well, I'm really enjoying my daily routine right now.
I'd like to continue to enjoy being on my own.
I want to make more and more memories!
What is today's fashionable point?
I put all my accessories together with hearts today.
This heart pin and
and the color bo accessories of Ms. Inaba and Mr. Liquium.
is the key point.
It's so cute!
What do you want to do in the next 6 months at the age of 18?
I would like to do more solo visual-kei work.
Thank you very much.
The question that caught my attention was this.
You released your first photo book on Valentine's Day this year.
You mentioned in the backstory that you took out the salt.
What did you do?
Well, I really didn't take any salt at all
I didn't take any salt at all one day before the shoot.
I drank a lot of soups and other drinks during the preparation period before that.
Soups also contain salt, so I ate sweet potatoes and jelly.
I ate sweet potatoes and jelly.
Cool.
Before the first day, I did this the day before the shoot.
I ate a lot of Okinawan food with all the staff on the night after the first day of shooting.
So after that, I didn't want it to affect the second day of shooting.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I half-bathed myself to death.
That's great!
So you worked out a lot.
Yes, I worked hard.
I asked you, "What do you want to do with your juice juice? I asked you what your daily life is like now.
I'm spending more time with the members than with my family, but I'm really enjoying my daily life, and I feel that time passes by so quickly.
I'd like to spend my time with them, cherishing each and every day and enjoying every minute of it.
I'd like to spend my time with you and enjoy every day.
I'm Natsuyaki Miyabi.
I'm Tashiro Sumi from "Tea in the Rain".
I'll continue to cook.
So what shall we cook this time?
Today we have wagyu beef tagliata.
With balsamic sauce.
Yes, sir.
I don't cook these days.
But I used to cook at home when I was little.
I remember that a little bit today.
I'd like to be able to improve even more.
It looks like barbecued meat.
This is it.
It looks so delicious!
It's like a sauce.
Hey, it's amazing!
So, where do we start this time?
I'd like to start grilling the meat.
Okay, let's cook it.
Okay, let's do it.
The heat should be about medium.
Medium heat.
The first one is the most important.
It's very important.
You see, this is how it's done.
Move it.
Yes, sir.
It's okay if it's small.
But for a steak like this, you don't move it.
Oh, I don't move it.
Don't move it
Nice and snug.
I just want to get the oil under here.
Perfectly done. The browning is perfect.
It's so beautiful.
Okay, hold that.
Let it sit for a minute.
Now, put the butter in here.
Yes, 10 grams of butter.
That's great.
It's called aloozé.
Alosé?
Alosé.
Do you know what it is?
I don't know.
Yes, I do.
What is arrosé?
What is Alozée?
Alozée means this... alozée.
That's it.
Melt the butter.
Put this butter on top of this.
To pour it over.
I want you to take this one, too.
Slowly like this.
Put it all over.
I want you to put it in the oil and heat it up.
Try it!
Looks delicious.
Is it done?
It's done.
It's perfect.
I've got goose bumps.
Looks good.
It's pretty good.
Can you stop this for a second?
Yes, sir.
Smells good.
It's a little thick.
I'd like to burn the sides, too.
Yes, sir.
I love meat.
That's right.
It's great, isn't it?
Looks good.
Yum! Yum! Yum!
So, you know, it's almost perfect.
Okay.
You can take it out here.
Yes, sir.
Just by doing this arrozetto.
It's like eating at a restaurant.
It's like eating at a restaurant, isn't it?
It's like a restaurant, isn't it?
If you cut it now...
It's only about 30 degrees inside.
Oh, that's right.
It's not good to eat them.
We put them in the oven to heat them slowly.
I see.
Put it in the oven at 170 degrees.
Please.
After 2 minutes, take the meat out and let it rest for 2 minutes.
Then put it in the oven for another 2 minutes.
Take it out again and let it rest for 2 minutes.
Repeat.
Repeat 5 times.
Here's the point, Miyabiz!
The point!
Rest is important!
It's important to take a break!
Butter is poured on me hot.
I'm pretty tired.
It's been in the oven too.
That's a lot of butter.
It makes it taut.
If you leave it in the oven for a long time...
they get tired.
What happens when it gets tired?
The juice comes out.
The juices come out.
Break!
I'm going to use this break time to talk to you again.
I'd like to talk about the group this time.
I'd like to talk a little bit about the group.
Ocha-no-Uma is doing a lot of live performances.
We are currently on a 47 prefectures tour.
We did this tour last year.
We're going to start it again this spring.
It's great!
The setlist is different from last year.
We released our first album last time.
We played some of those songs.
And some shuffle songs.
We can listen to songs from each unit.
I really want to deliver more songs to you all as soon as possible
I want to do my best!
What kind of shuffle songs are on the album?
Yes, that's right.
There are three teams.
Each of them is an uplifting song for idols.
And some of them are cool songs.
And some are a little sad.
Sadness, too.
The songs they sing...
Please talk.
I see.
I'm sure it'll be fun.
While we're talking.
I'm going to insert this.
Yes, ma'am.
Okay.
Okay, let's put the meat...
Aluminum foil.
And mix it.
The surface will not dry out and it will cool down.
And the residual heat should slowly work its way in.
It should be good.
Here it is.
The pan you just cooked the meat in.
Don't wash this.
When you turn on the heat, throw away the butter.
Add a tablespoon of mirin.
How's that sound?
How is it?
It's bleeding.
It's on fire. Great.
This is the teacher, with the difficult name...
Alozeresso.
It's not Alozée.
This is different.
Degrasse.
It means "degrasse.
Degrasse. Another difficult name.
Deglace is now fire?
It's not fire. It's more like mixing.
It's like mixing the meat with alcohol to dissolve the juices.
This sauce looks delicious.
I'm sure it's perfect.
It's perfect.
Okay, now I want to slice the beef fins into thin slices.
You don't have to slice it that thin, but...
But today, I'm going to slice it at a bit of a slant because it's a needle hole.
It's kind of soft.
It's soft.
This is a beef fin.
It feels like I'm cutting it.
Smooth.
It's gorgeous this time.
It's so gorgeous.
Yes, it is.
Vegetables
Yes, sir.
Tomatoes for decoration.
Yes.
A few fruit tomatoes for decoration.
Colorful.
Right next to it.
Yes.
Cute.
Yellow
Yes
I would like to serve it
Serve
Yes, please
First of all, we'll have a salad, a mixed salad.
Yes, please.
In the middle.
You may have quite a few of these.
Not too much, yes.
That's enough.
Cute.
Like this?
Yes.
The meat is, you know, for this potato.
Potatoes.
Or you can arrange them like this.
Yes.
It's all in your taste, isn't it?
Like this?
It's really colorful.
It's very colorful.
Colors, yes.
The color is coming out, isn't it?
The color is really coming out, and the redness is increasing.
Yes, sir.
The teacher's favorite.
Cheese.
Oh, leciano leciano.
Delicious.
We're not going to shave it today.
We're going to peel it.
Oh, wow.
Oh, my God.
Did you see that?
Surprise swivel.
It's buckwheat.
Oh, wow.
Oh, my God.
Oh!
It's good. It's very good.
I think it's good.
Yes, sir.
It's OK.
It's done.
Wagyu Beef Tagliata
Yes, sir.
Balsamic.
Yay!
Wagyu Beef Tagliata is ready!
Yes, sir.
How do you like it, Sumire?
Yes, I heard it has a very stylish name!
I wondered if I would be able to master such an amazing beef fin.
But I'm so happy that I was able to make it this way, using various processes and techniques!
I'm glad.
Now, please try it!
Bon appétit!
It's so delicious!
I tasted a lot of things earlier.
Is it done? It's got the sauce and everything.
It's very delicious.
How was it cooking?
I haven't had a chance to cook recently.
I wasn't sure if I would be able to cook it well.
I wondered if I would be able to cook well, but it was a great experience for me to learn how to cook such a wonderful dish from the teacher.
It was a great experience for me.
I would like to serve this kind of food to my parents and other family members next time.
I'm sure you might be busy with live concerts and so on.
I hope you will try it at home or on your days off!
That's all for now, Hello Kitchen!
Thank you very much!
Risa Irie of Juice=Juice and
Risa Irie of Juice=Juice and Yumi Kasai of Tsubaki Factory will be presenting "Hello! STE, presented by Risa Irie of Juice=Juice and Yumi Kasai of
Juice=Juice will start on April 20
Tsubaki Factory will start their tour on May 3.
Since it's just before their tour, we've chosen a live video of a song from the other group.
I've selected live videos of the other group's songs that make me want to sing along with them, so let me introduce them to you in order!
The Juice=Juice song I chose that makes me want to sing along is
Magic of Love
This time, I'm going to show you the live video from Juice=Juice's Tenth Anniversary Concert Tour.
Let's watch the video of Juice=Juice @ Budokan together!
Counting
Shine.
It's amazing how everyone can enjoy the free movement like this with their friends
Watch this one too.
Sorin was crying
Seeing her like this made me so happy.
Other groups don't have such a free flow going on.
That's right.
Oh, wow! Oh, so many things are happening.
I want to call with you here.
Misearch.
I definitely want to say this call live!
Yeah, I really wanted to listen to this with my earpiece out.
You did?
It's a moment of heartfelt happiness.
I'm listening with my earphones out.
I'm so glad you guys said that.
It makes me happy.
And this girl's hair.
Lovely, it looks good on her.
Everyone was personally happy to see
the outfit in their own men's colors.
Light purple.
I see.
I was personally happy for some reason.
But you know, I'm happy because it's the member's color.
They all look great together.
Juice=Juice's costumes
I had an image that most of them were red or black.
but the light purple and light purple are amazing!
It looks good on you.
I'm so happy!
As you can see, Juice=Juice
Juice=Juice is a very talented artist.
I think your voice is so beautiful
And her singing voice is so beautiful.
and her singing ability is amazing.
I felt happy when I listened to them.
And also
I chose this song because
Where are you?
I'm right here, right now!
You're Lisa, right?
How does it feel to be called Juice?
What?
Wait!
But since I got this song...
I got the nickname "Risachi".
Until then, I was always called Risa-chan.
This song is the reason I got the nickname Risachi.
It's a very memorable phrase and song for me.
Tomoko Kanazawa was the first person to sing this song.
I liked it even then, but
But after listening to various versions of the song
I've listened to many different versions of the song, including the current Juice=Juice and the previous Juice=Juice.
It's so wonderful to listen to this magic of love
I really like it.
Thank you very much.
Next, I chose Tsubaki Factory's song that makes me want to sing along with them.
Reishi no Camellia (Beautiful Camellia).
This time it's from Tsubaki Factory Concert 2021
Let's watch the video of Camellia Nippon Budokan Special together!
I miss them so much!
cute
I missed
First time on stage? Is it not?
It was my first show.
It was like a continuation of the manager's style.
But now I'm here with the members of Tsubaki Factory.
with the members of Tsubaki Factory
I'm going to perform with the members of Tsubaki Factory.
It was the first time to perform at Budokan
I was so nervous.
I can tell you're nervous.
I can see it in your eyes.
Yes, I can.
And the unison of the two of us singing together.
It was so beautiful when we were there.
It was really nice. Thank you.
I love your expression here.
I'm so happy.
And I also thought that this leg looked like it would be difficult to do the step.
I knew it.
I'm not used to singing while stepping.
I wasn't used to singing while stepping.
So it was really difficult.
Luno-chan was really jumping around.
I remember that.
I knew the rhythm.
Yo Furuno was the rhythm.
That's great.
Yes, she was a trainee.
Yes, I've seen the video.
I've seen the footage.
Yes, including us.
There are seven of us.
Four at Tsubaki Factory and three at Juice Chus.
I mean...
The first Budokan
I was watching their first Budokan
I was watching from the audience
I almost cried from the opening of the show.
I remember how cool he was.
I remember how cool it was.
Rhythm Up
I was so impressed by the performance of this song by the four of them.
I'm so glad.
I guess it's a difficult song if you just look at the lyrics card.
But it's a cute song with a bright capture.
I was so impressed by the 4 of them singing it.
I liked the song to begin with.
I liked it to begin with, but I liked it even more when the four of us sang it.
So I chose this song.
I'm so happy!
I don't know how to put it.
I was really inspired by the friendly competition with each other
I thought again that it was that live concert that gave us a lot of inspiration to work hard and compete with each other.
Thank you very much. I'm very happy.
He's a shy boy. I know he's shy, but...
Oh, ah, ah, my heart is pounding, my heart is pounding.
Are you lying? Hey, hey, hey, hey! France, brother!
I don't like it. I'm just messing with you.
Oh, Ah Ah, he doesn't even notice the new nails and haircut?
You know, sometimes you have to compliment me, get used to it, tell me I'm pretty.
Or maybe you'd like to fall in love with someone who smells like alpred.
I'm going to fall in love with someone exciting.
Life is a prayer. Case O' Case.
Matching burgers, O-Case, O-Case.
I'm actually really into you.
I don't have one, I don't have one, I'm standing on my own
You know
I'm missing some vague line.
I can't measure up, I can't measure up, I know I can't measure up
Gundam.
It's not Gundam.
Your love, love, love
You're gonna have to stop now.
Sorry, my baby.
You don't have it
Love Love Love
You Give Me Give Me Your Love Yeah
Love Give Me More Your Love
I miss you
I can't see you.
You're always asking me out
Who's gonna feed me? Slow down, slow down, slow down, slow down.
I can't stop asking you where you want to eat.
Romantic.
I want a tent.
I'd be so embarrassed.
I'm waiting for the words.
When you call my name
Yes or Yes
You're too kind
And your shy smile
I love it.
I'm gone. I'm gone. I'm gone.
I'm all about the things... of endless love...
But is it true?
I just wanted your I love you.
I can't measure it. Nothing. Nothing.
Love's not a simple weight.
Your love, even love
It's a clumsy thing.
My baby
Words, Music, Arrangement: Hatsune Miku
Arranged by Miku Hatsune
Oh, forgive me
I don't have it, I don't have it, I don't have it
I don't have anything, do I?
When are you going to say something like that, so I'm not even going to have enough vague lines and whining.
I can't tell, I know I can't tell, it's not that easy.
You, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love
You love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love
Today's effort will lead to tomorrow
Risa Irie of Juice Chus and
and Yumi Kasai of Tsubaki Factory present "Haloste".
It's time for us to say goodbye.
Here's an announcement!
Juice Chusu's 18th new single will be released on May 15th!
This time, it's a triple A-side single of "Tokyo Bura Nai Mono Love Aiko".
It's a triple A-side single.
All of the songs are different from each other and have completely different tunes.
Since this is the last single of Mr. Uemura's career, I thought it would be nice to have some of his main songs as well.
As it was Mr. Uemura's last single, some of the songs were his main ones, while others were costumes with his colors.
Some of the songs are Uemura-san's main songs, and some of the costumes are Uemura-san's colors.
They are all very nice singles.
Please check them out!
Looking forward to it!
Yes, Tsubaki Factory Concert Tour 2023 Autumn Atara yo!
Riko Yamagishi and Yume Kishimoto's graduation special
The DVD and Blu-ray of AKATSUKI was released today!
Yes, you can see Ms. Yamagishi and Ms. Kishimoto's graduation
I hope you can see their graduation performances!
Yes, and Juice=Juice concert tour 2024
One Line will start on April 20!
This will be Juice=Juice's spring tour.
This time, we will be performing 22 concerts in 11 venues.
We will be performing 22 shows in 11 venues this time.
So I'm thinking it's going to be a physical challenge for me.
I think it's going to be a physical challenge for me.
I'm going to work on my stamina and enjoy it until the end of the tour.
Yes, Tsubaki Factory Concert Tour 2024 Spring
Camon Everybody will start on May 3!
Yes, this will be the last tour for the leader, Sora Arainoki, and the first tour for the new members.
This will also be the first tour for the new members.
Please look forward to it!
And Juice=Juice will hold a public recording event in Osaka.
Juice=Juice will hold a public recording event in Osaka!
The date is April 29th and it will be called FM Osaka Juice=Juice YOU STORY!
We hope it will be a special event again
We hope you will come and join us!
Tsubaki Factory will be performing at Sakofest Universe on April 21!
We are very excited to be a part of this event, and we are looking forward to seeing you all there!
We hope you will all come and see us!
And on May 12th, Tsubaki Factory will be performing at Galafes Narase with Halo Pro trainee unit 24.
We are going to perform at "Galafest Narase! Kizuna Fanfare.
We will do our best to make both Tsubaki Factory and Halopro Trainee Unit 24 excited!
And Tsubaki Factory will perform in Shanghai on May 18!
We're really looking forward to going abroad again.
We will do our best to tour not only in Shanghai but also more and more.
We will do our best so that we can tour overseas as well.
Haloste is a channel where Hello Project members will appear more and more!
New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday.
Please subscribe to our channel!
This time we have Risa Irie of Juice Chus and Yumi Kasai of Tsubaki Factory.
and Yumi Kasai of Tsubaki Factory.
Good bye!
Thank you for watching!